

Macadam Thomson

# Chosen name Makenzie Thomson



(506) 229-7495



Makenzieithomson@gmail.com



https://m0ooncake.github.io

## **SKILLS**

- Organization
- Technology
- Time Management
- Attention to Detail
- Problem Solving

## **HOBBIES**

- Gaming
- Historical European
  Martial Arts
- Photography
- Soldering
- Coding Projects

## **EDUCATION**

- Graduated Riverview
  High School in 2020
- Currently enrolled with Toronto Film School for Video Game Design and Development

#### **SUMMARY**

Well versed in organization, physical activity and very detail oriented. Four years of experience volunteering at a summer camp in Quebec that has archery, axe throwing, RC cars, swimming and more. Worked alongside colleagues to set up plans, organize events and keep things moving. Significant experience in vehicle detailing and rapidly changing work environments.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Volunteer at Camp Livingstone - Stanstead, QC Started in 2015 to 2019

- Regularly cleaned campgrounds, bathrooms, showers.
- Helped build a cedar fence around the RC track.
- Assisted and lead people through the cleanup of woods campgrounds and construction of stone stairs.
- Helped lead campers through ropes course, RC cars and axe throwing.

Backline worker at Arby's, Arby's - Moncton, NB May 2020 to May 2021

- Worked effectively in a high intensity environment while producing good and fast results.
- Able to communicate and work with teammates in a high stress situation.
- Able to multitask efficiently.

Detailer at Hertz rentals - Moncton, NB March 2022 to April 2023

- Maintained an excellent clean working environment.
- Efficiently cleaned, washed and prepared upwards of 15 cars a day with extreme detail and precision.
- Regularly needed to switch priorities and adapt to a rapidly changing work environment.

Detailer at Recar - Moncton, NB April 2023 to October 2023

- Exercise skill and speed detailing vehicles as they come in and on a need to do basis.
- Uses an assortment of industry chemicals and compounds to ensure the vehicle stays the best for as long as possible.
- Adapted to a changing environment and dedicatedly detail vehicles for 1-7 hours as required.